<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<Resume xmlns="http://ns.hr-xml.org/RecruitingAndStaffing/SEP-2_0"
		xsi:schemaLocation="http://ns.hr-xml.org/RecruitingAndStaffing/SEP-2_0 resume.xsd"
		xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
	<StructuredXMLResume>
		<ContactInfo>
			<PersonName>
				<FormattedName>Prerit Bhakta</FormattedName>
			</PersonName>
			<ContactMethod>
				<Mobile smsEnabled="true">
					<InternationalCountryCode>1</InternationalCountryCode>
					<NationalNumber>1</NationalNumber>
					<AreaCityCode>314</AreaCityCode>
					<SubscriberNumber>3690061</SubscriberNumber>
				</Mobile>
				<Fax>
					<InternationalCountryCode>1</InternationalCountryCode>
					<NationalNumber>1</NationalNumber>
					<AreaCityCode>314</AreaCityCode>
					<SubscriberNumber>9612324</SubscriberNumber>
				</Fax>
				<InternetEmailAddress>prerit.bhakta@gmail.com</InternetEmailAddress>
				<InternetWebAddress>http://prerit.com/</InternetWebAddress>
			</ContactMethod>
		</ContactInfo>
		<Objective>A dynamic and energetic individual who is committed to creating robust, cost-effective solutions for fast paced business environments. Transitioning into a more leadership/mentor role because of knowledge acquired through a combination of personal mentors and experience. Able to work on own initiative and as part of a team. Dedicated to maintaining high quality standards.</Objective>
		<EmploymentHistory>

			<!-- Technology Partners -->

			<EmployerOrg employerOrgType="agent">
				<EmployerOrgName>Technology Partners</EmployerOrgName>
				<EmployerContactInfo contactType="account manager">
					<PersonName>
						<FormattedName>Dwayne Norton</FormattedName>
					</PersonName>
					<ContactMethod>
						<Telephone>
							<InternationalCountryCode>1</InternationalCountryCode>
							<NationalNumber>1</NationalNumber>
							<AreaCityCode>314</AreaCityCode>
							<SubscriberNumber>6365191221</SubscriberNumber>
						</Telephone>
						<Fax>
							<InternationalCountryCode>1</InternationalCountryCode>
							<NationalNumber>1</NationalNumber>
							<AreaCityCode>314</AreaCityCode>
							<SubscriberNumber>6365190421</SubscriberNumber>
						</Fax>
						<InternetEmailAddress>dnorton@tech-partners.com</InternetEmailAddress>
						<InternetWebAddress>http://www.tech-partners.com/</InternetWebAddress>
						<PostalAddress>
							<CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
							<PostalCode>63005</PostalCode>
							<Region>MO</Region>
							<Municipality>Chesterfield</Municipality>
							<DeliveryAddress>
								<AddressLine>16640</AddressLine>
								<StreetName>Chesterfield Grove Road</StreetName>
								<Unit>Suite 190</Unit>
							</DeliveryAddress>
						</PostalAddress>
					</ContactMethod>
				</EmployerContactInfo>
				<PositionHistory positionType="contractToHire">
					<Title>Developer of "Creo Framework"</Title>
					<OrgName organizationType="company">
						<OrganizationName>Maritz</OrganizationName>
					</OrgName>
					<OrgInfo>
						<WebSite>http://www.maritz.com/</WebSite>
					</OrgInfo>
					<Description>
						To fulfill the training needs of Maritz Learning's clients, a scalable and robust architecture was needed as a foundation to rapidly develop custom applications. The Creo Framework, originally built upon .NET 1.1, was the solution to creating customized pluggable components to train people via different methods such as podcasts, email, voicemail messages, etc. As one of the developers, my accomplishments in this application consisted of the following:

						* Introduced .NET 2.0 and SQL Server 2005 to the team members by successfully lobbying to management about the new features and enhancements associated to the new version *
						* Mentored team members on the new features of .NET 2.0 and SQL Server 2005 and upgraded the .NET project files *
						* Helped test Creo in terms of performance, pointed out bottlenecks and helped move the framework from a .NET remoting based framework to an inprocess one *
						* Finished implementing a previously unfinished privilege handling based on user accounts for business objects *
						* Created a list of enhancements and code optimizations and shared it with fellow team members *

						Environment: ASP.NET, C#, Design Patterns, OOP, SQL Server, UML
					</Description>
					<StartDate>
						<YearMonth>2006-08</YearMonth>
					</StartDate>
				</PositionHistory>
			</EmployerOrg>

			<!-- Advanced Resources -->

			<EmployerOrg employerOrgType="agent">
				<EmployerOrgName>Advanced Resources</EmployerOrgName>
				<EmployerContactInfo contactType="president">
					<PersonName>
						<FormattedName>Frank Ehlers</FormattedName>
					</PersonName>
					<ContactMethod>
						<Telephone>
							<InternationalCountryCode>1</InternationalCountryCode>
							<NationalNumber>1</NationalNumber>
							<AreaCityCode>636</AreaCityCode>
							<SubscriberNumber>6367774141</SubscriberNumber>
						</Telephone>
						<Fax>
							<InternationalCountryCode>1</InternationalCountryCode>
							<NationalNumber>1</NationalNumber>
							<AreaCityCode>636</AreaCityCode>
							<SubscriberNumber>6367774142</SubscriberNumber>
						</Fax>
						<InternetEmailAddress>frank.ehlers@advancedresources.net</InternetEmailAddress>
						<InternetWebAddress>http://www.advancedresources.net/</InternetWebAddress>
						<PostalAddress>
							<CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
							<PostalCode>63017</PostalCode>
							<Region>MO</Region>
							<Municipality>Chesterfield</Municipality>
							<DeliveryAddress>
								<AddressLine>15450</AddressLine>
								<StreetName>South Outer Forty Drive</StreetName>
							</DeliveryAddress>
						</PostalAddress>
					</ContactMethod>
				</EmployerContactInfo>
				<PositionHistory positionType="contractToHire">
					<Title>Developer of "Reuters.com"</Title>
					<OrgName organizationType="company">
						<OrganizationName>Reuters</OrganizationName>
					</OrgName>
					<OrgInfo>
						<WebSite>http://www.reuters.com/</WebSite>
					</OrgInfo>
					<Description>
						Reuters, one of the most respected and trustworthy news organizations, is world renown for it's ability to deliver up to the minute news from around the world. One key component of this core business requirement is a massive, yet robust website that is efficient and scalable. As one of the developers, my accomplishments in this application consisted of the following:

						* Designed and developed a multilingual online hub for Reuters.com users to catch up on current events by watching free online news casts by using custom Reuters.com Design Patterns and ASP.NET caching *
						* Architected the ASP.NET error handling to better inform the developers and support staff of the root causes of reproducible .NET errors in every stage of the development lifecycle *
						* Mentored other developers by creating code samples of .NET best practices by finding mistakes and/or inefficiencies in the source code and sharing them at the weekly developers meeting *
						* Retroactively implemented .NET best practices gained from analyzing the source code in order to optimize the system *

						Environment: ASP.NET, C#, CSS, Design Patterns, HTML, JavaScript, NAnt, OOP, XML
					</Description>
					<StartDate>
						<YearMonth>2005-10</YearMonth>
					</StartDate>
					<EndDate>
						<YearMonth>2006-08</YearMonth>
					</EndDate>
				</PositionHistory>
			</EmployerOrg>

			<!-- Stockell -->

			<EmployerOrg employerOrgType="agent">
				<EmployerOrgName>Stockell</EmployerOrgName>
				<EmployerContactInfo contactType="account manager">
					<PersonName>
						<FormattedName>Greg Shafer</FormattedName>
					</PersonName>
					<ContactMethod>
						<Telephone>
							<InternationalCountryCode>1</InternationalCountryCode>
							<NationalNumber>1</NationalNumber>
							<AreaCityCode>636</AreaCityCode>
							<SubscriberNumber>6365379530</SubscriberNumber>
						</Telephone>
						<Fax>
							<InternationalCountryCode>1</InternationalCountryCode>
							<NationalNumber>1</NationalNumber>
							<AreaCityCode>636</AreaCityCode>
							<SubscriberNumber>6365375542</SubscriberNumber>
						</Fax>
						<InternetEmailAddress>gshafer@stockell.com</InternetEmailAddress>
						<InternetWebAddress>http://www.stockell.com/</InternetWebAddress>
						<PostalAddress>
							<CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
							<PostalCode>63017</PostalCode>
							<Region>MO</Region>
							<Municipality>Chesterfield</Municipality>
							<DeliveryAddress>
								<AddressLine>15400</AddressLine>
								<StreetName>South Outer Forty Drive</StreetName>
							</DeliveryAddress>
						</PostalAddress>
					</ContactMethod>
				</EmployerContactInfo>
				<PositionHistory positionType="contractToHire">
					<Title>Developer of "Digecenter"</Title>
					<OrgName organizationType="company">
						<OrganizationName>Jerome Group</OrganizationName>
					</OrgName>
					<OrgInfo>
						<WebSite>http://www.jeromegroup.com/</WebSite>
					</OrgInfo>
					<Description>
						The ability for marketing departments to reach their customers quickly and efficiently via mass mailing is a problem that the Jerome Group provides a solution for. The Digecenter application is one of the tools that were created to expedite this process by allowing the Jerome Group's clients to customize their marketing needs. As one of the developers, my accomplishments in this application consisted of the following:

						* Analyzed, architected (via UML static structure diagrams) and implemented "Gang of Four" Design Patterns in VB.NET to simplify object hierarchy, promote object reuse and improve overall efficiency of core business functionality *
						* Responsible for the research, design, and implementation of Opus online proofing Web Services integration into current infrastructure as well as producing impact analysis documentation and flow chart diagrams *
						* Optimized ASP.NET and WinForms code to perform significantly faster by utilizing a combination of lightweight data structures, .NET best practices, object oriented design principles and SQL Server performance enhancement techniques such as utilizing stored procedures, efficient query writing and indexes by using SQL Server Index Tuning Wizard *
						* Mentored other developers in object oriented programming techniques, .NET and SQL Server best practices, guidelines to follow and general advice on efficient .NET and SQL Server coding as well as the .NET object hierarchy *

						Environment: ASP.NET, Design Patterns, OOP, SOAP, SQL Server, UML, VB.NET, Web Services, WinForms, XML, XSLT
					</Description>
					<StartDate>
						<YearMonth>2005-03</YearMonth>
					</StartDate>
					<EndDate>
						<YearMonth>2005-09</YearMonth>
					</EndDate>
				</PositionHistory>
			</EmployerOrg>

			<!-- Technology Partners -->

			<EmployerOrg employerOrgType="agent">
				<EmployerOrgName>Technology Partners</EmployerOrgName>
				<EmployerContactInfo contactType="account manager">
					<PersonName>
						<FormattedName>Dwayne Norton</FormattedName>
					</PersonName>
					<ContactMethod>
						<Telephone>
							<InternationalCountryCode>1</InternationalCountryCode>
							<NationalNumber>1</NationalNumber>
							<AreaCityCode>314</AreaCityCode>
							<SubscriberNumber>6365191221</SubscriberNumber>
						</Telephone>
						<Fax>
							<InternationalCountryCode>1</InternationalCountryCode>
							<NationalNumber>1</NationalNumber>
							<AreaCityCode>314</AreaCityCode>
							<SubscriberNumber>6365190421</SubscriberNumber>
						</Fax>
						<InternetEmailAddress>dnorton@tech-partners.com</InternetEmailAddress>
						<InternetWebAddress>http://www.tech-partners.com/</InternetWebAddress>
						<PostalAddress>
							<CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
							<PostalCode>63005</PostalCode>
							<Region>MO</Region>
							<Municipality>Chesterfield</Municipality>
							<DeliveryAddress>
								<AddressLine>16640</AddressLine>
								<StreetName>Chesterfield Grove Road</StreetName>
								<Unit>Suite 190</Unit>
							</DeliveryAddress>
						</PostalAddress>
					</ContactMethod>
				</EmployerContactInfo>
				<PositionHistory positionType="contractToHire">
					<Title>Developer of "Household Rewards"</Title>
					<OrgName organizationType="company">
						<OrganizationName>Maritz</OrganizationName>
					</OrgName>
					<OrgInfo>
						<WebSite>http://www.maritz.com/</WebSite>
					</OrgInfo>
					<Description>
						As one of Maritz's many financial clients, Household International charged Maritz to create a rewards fulfillment system to create a unique customer experience. In the program, thousands of orders are created and fulfilled on a daily basis by Household International's customers. These products represent tens of thousands of dollars in merchandise and an enormous amount of money spent to acquire the necessary points to redeem them. As one of the developers, my accomplishments in this application consisted of the following:

						* Developed and maintained an object oriented C# based ASP.NET e-commerce web application which utilizes SSL to secure sensitive credit card information transmitted over the internet *
						* Designed, developed and implemented the migration of customer history from a similar but distinctly different SQL Server database model of an older ASP based e-commerce web application *
						* Architected and developed SQL Server DTS packages to seamlessly integrate 2 independent systems on a daily basis in order for customers to receive their most up-to-date account information *
						* Implemented SQL Server optimizations to speed up the transaction times of orders on the e-commerce web application in order to enhance the user's customer experience and to allow more concurrent users *
						* Leveraged CSS and the database to create themes in order for Household to have many different programs associated with the various credit cards and differing functionality for each credit card *

						Environment: ASP.NET, C#, CSS, Design Patterns, DTS, OOP, SQL Server, UML
					</Description>
					<StartDate>
						<YearMonth>2004-04</YearMonth>
					</StartDate>
					<EndDate>
						<YearMonth>2005-04</YearMonth>
					</EndDate>
				</PositionHistory>
			</EmployerOrg>

			<!-- Envision -->

			<EmployerOrg employerOrgType="agent">
				<EmployerOrgName>Envision</EmployerOrgName>
				<EmployerContactInfo contactType="vice president">
					<PersonName>
						<FormattedName>Hans Gerwitz</FormattedName>
					</PersonName>
					<ContactMethod>
						<Telephone>
							<InternationalCountryCode>1</InternationalCountryCode>
							<NationalNumber>1</NationalNumber>
							<AreaCityCode>314</AreaCityCode>
							<SubscriberNumber>9935858</SubscriberNumber>
						</Telephone>
						<Fax>
							<InternationalCountryCode>1</InternationalCountryCode>
							<NationalNumber>1</NationalNumber>
							<AreaCityCode>314</AreaCityCode>
							<SubscriberNumber>9936674</SubscriberNumber>
						</Fax>
						<InternetEmailAddress>hans.gerwitz@envision.com</InternetEmailAddress>
						<InternetWebAddress>http://www.envision.com/</InternetWebAddress>
						<PostalAddress>
							<CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
							<PostalCode>63141</PostalCode>
							<Region>MO</Region>
							<Municipality>Saint Louis</Municipality>
							<DeliveryAddress>
								<AddressLine>11605</AddressLine>
								<StreetName>Studt Avenue</StreetName>
								<Unit>Suite 120</Unit>
							</DeliveryAddress>
						</PostalAddress>
					</ContactMethod>
				</EmployerContactInfo>
				<PositionHistory positionType="contractToHire">
					<Title>Developer of "Market Development Tool"</Title>
					<OrgName organizationType="company">
						<OrganizationName>Anheuser-Busch</OrganizationName>
					</OrgName>
					<OrgInfo>
						<WebSite>http://www.anheuser-busch.com/</WebSite>
					</OrgInfo>
					<Description>
						The suite of applications known as the Market Development Tool (MDT) written under the direction of the Anheuser-Busch Sales Department consists of 3 separate applications which when linked together, provide invaluable market data to both upper management and field sales personnel. MDT exists in three forms in order to serve each of its three distinct user bases by targeting their specific needs. The total user base of MDT is well over a thousand users. In its first year of inception, MDT has been tremendously successful and has scored over 4 out of 5 on recent surveys. Originally, MDT began as a project with only myself and two other developers, but its importance and functionality quickly expanded and a total of seven developers were required to execute the business needs of Anheuser-Busch. As one of the developers, my accomplishments in this application consisted of the following:

						* Instrumental in introducing the first .NET project written in C# at Anheuser-Busch because of my prior experience with the technology (self taught) *
						* Architected a multi-tier suite of 3 applications (2 web based ASP.NET applications and a Windows application) that reuses common business and ADO.NET data access components to reduce development time and cost against both Oracle and SQL Server *
						* Solely designed, developed and implemented one of the web applications to utilize SOAP, XML and Web Services as the data source and transportation, XSLT as the transformation source, and XPATH as the bridge between both sources to produce an XHTML interface *
						* Implemented a marketing initiative in 2 of the applications which annually manages over one hundred million dollars annually by tracking promotional expenditures *
						* Created the look and feel of the first application and leveraged it in the other applications to create a seamless suite of applications to reduce the learning curve of all end users *
						* Leveraged CSS to create brand based themes and the ability to change font sizes to the application to enhance the user's experience *
						* Mentored the less experienced developers in both C#, ASP.NET and the .NET framework *

						Environment: ASP.NET, C#, CSS, Design Patterns, Oracle, OOP, SOAP, SQL Server, UML, Web Services, WinForms, XHTML, XML, XSLT
					</Description>
					<StartDate>
						<YearMonth>2002-09</YearMonth>
					</StartDate>
					<EndDate>
						<YearMonth>2004-04</YearMonth>
					</EndDate>
				</PositionHistory>
				<PositionHistory positionType="contractToHire">
					<Title>Developer of "SOTD Evaluations"</Title>
					<OrgName organizationType="company">
						<OrganizationName>Anheuser-Busch</OrganizationName>
					</OrgName>
					<OrgInfo>
						<WebSite>http://www.anheuser-busch.com/</WebSite>
					</OrgInfo>
					<Description>
						Sales Operations Training and Development (SOTD) department required an application that could both generate and evaluate dynamic surveys taken by members of each training session. In this way, each member of the SOTD group could track his or her effectiveness in training other Anheuser-Busch employees. This web-based tool featured many rollup capabilities such as the ability to generate graphical reports on the status of an individual trainer or survey type. As the sole developer of SOTD Evaluations, my accomplishments in this application consisted of the following:

						* Architected and implemented an ASP driven web based application written using CSS, XHTML and XML to build and maintain dynamic surveys *
						* Created a secure administration section for team members to perform complex administration tasks such creating, editing and deleting surveys as well as running complex reports on the effectiveness of Anheuser-Busch trainers *
						* Utilized CSS to graphically display individual survey results or group survey results to administrators of the application *
						* Used the MSXML component of SQL Server to automatically produce XML as its native output in order to use XSLT as the transformation source *
						* Leveraged CSS to create brand based themes and the ability to change font sizes to the application to enhance the user's experience *

						Environment: ASP, CSS, SQL Server, XHTML, XML, XSLT
					</Description>
					<StartDate>
						<YearMonth>2002-06</YearMonth>
					</StartDate>
					<EndDate>
						<YearMonth>2002-09</YearMonth>
					</EndDate>
				</PositionHistory>

				<PositionHistory positionType="contractToHire">
					<Title>Developer of "Contact Gatherer"</Title>
					<OrgName organizationType="company">
						<OrganizationName>Marketing Direct</OrganizationName>
					</OrgName>
					<OrgInfo>
						<WebSite>http://www.marketingdirect.com/</WebSite>
					</OrgInfo>
					<Description>
						In order to further reach consumers for Marketing Direct's clients, a database application was required to harvest the consumers' information. Marketing Direct's clients consists of many direct to consumer agencies around the United States who required an automated application to dynamically generate lists of customers on a daily basis. As the sole developer, my accomplishments in this application consisted of the following:

						* Designed and implemented a SQL Server database tool for data extraction of potential clients from 3rd party documents *
						* Convinced the 3rd parties to utilize XML documents instead of transferring tab delimited text files in order for simplicity, data integrity and future upgradeability *
						* Architected complex AI logic into the tool to eliminate duplicate contacts thus saving Marketing Direct money by having a much more focused customer base *
						* Leveraged SQL Server's features to both expedite development time and transform the tool from a manual process to an automatic one *

						Environment: SQL Server, XML, XSLT
					</Description>
					<StartDate>
						<YearMonth>2001-06</YearMonth>
					</StartDate>
					<EndDate>
						<YearMonth>2001-07</YearMonth>
					</EndDate>
				</PositionHistory>

				<PositionHistory positionType="internship">
					<Title>Developer of "Webport-Ecom"</Title>
					<OrgName organizationType="company">
						<OrganizationName>DHL</OrganizationName>
					</OrgName>
					<OrgInfo>
						<WebSite>http://www.dhl.com/</WebSite>
					</OrgInfo>
					<Description>
						As a global logistical company, DHL required a secure web-based application to track both air and ocean shipments made by their client companies. A complete list of ports and countries around the world as well as the ability to dynamically create PDFs of shipping documents is just a small part of the application known as Webport-Ecom. As a developer, my accomplishments in this application consisted of the following:

						* Worked in a team of 3 developers to design and implement an ASP and COM/COM+ based solution to track global shipments *
						* Implemented the administration section to add, modify and delete system wide data such as shipping ports and countries *
						* Designed a security model around SSL to prevent unauthorized entry into the application *
						* Organized and used Acrobat FDF template documents as the basis for the dynamic generation of PDF shipping documents *

						Environment: ASP, COM/COM+, SQL Server
					</Description>
					<StartDate>
						<YearMonth>2000-07</YearMonth>
					</StartDate>
					<EndDate>
						<YearMonth>2001-06</YearMonth>
					</EndDate>
				</PositionHistory>
			</EmployerOrg>
		</EmploymentHistory>
		<EducationHistory>
			<SchoolOrInstitution schoolType="university">
				<SchoolName>Saint Louis University</SchoolName>
				<LocationSummary>
					<Municipality>Saint Louis</Municipality>
					<Region>MO</Region>
					<CountryCode>US</CountryCode>
				</LocationSummary>
				<OrganizationUnit organizationType="subSchool">College of Arts and Sciences</OrganizationUnit>
				<Degree degreeType="Bachelors">
					<DegreeName>Computer Science</DegreeName>
					<DegreeDate>
						<YearMonth>2001-05</YearMonth>
					</DegreeDate>
				</Degree>
				<Major>Computer Science</Major>
				<Minor>Mathematics</Minor>
				<Measure measureType="GPA">
					<MeasureSystem>4.0</MeasureSystem>
					<MeasureValue>3.6</MeasureValue>
				</Measure>
				<DatesOfAttendance>
					<StartDate>
						<YearMonth>1997-09</YearMonth>
					</StartDate>
					<EndDate>
						<YearMonth>2001-05</YearMonth>
					</EndDate>
				</DatesOfAttendance>
				<Comments>Graduated with Honors (Magna Cum Laude)</Comments>
			</SchoolOrInstitution>
		</EducationHistory>
		<Qualifications>
			<!-- Languages -->

			<Competency name="C">
				<TaxonomyId id="Languages"
							description="Languages" />
			</Competency>
			<Competency name="C++">
				<TaxonomyId id="Languages"
							description="Languages" />
			</Competency>
			<Competency name="C#">
				<TaxonomyId id="Languages"
							description="Languages" />
			</Competency>
			<Competency name="CSS">
				<TaxonomyId id="Languages"
							description="Languages" />
			</Competency>
			<Competency name="HTML">
				<TaxonomyId id="Languages"
							description="Languages" />
			</Competency>
			<Competency name="JavaScript">
				<TaxonomyId id="Languages"
							description="Languages" />
			</Competency>
			<Competency name="SQL">
				<TaxonomyId id="Languages"
							description="Languages" />
			</Competency>
			<Competency name="VB">
				<TaxonomyId id="Languages"
							description="Languages" />
			</Competency>
			<Competency name="VB.NET">
				<TaxonomyId id="Languages"
							description="Languages" />
			</Competency>
			<Competency name="VBScript">
				<TaxonomyId id="Languages"
							description="Languages" />
			</Competency>
			<Competency name="XHTML">
				<TaxonomyId id="Languages"
							description="Languages" />
			</Competency>
			<Competency name="XML">
				<TaxonomyId id="Languages"
							description="Languages" />
			</Competency>
			<Competency name="XML Schema">
				<TaxonomyId id="Languages"
							description="Languages" />
			</Competency>
			<Competency name="XPATH">
				<TaxonomyId id="Languages"
							description="Languages" />
			</Competency>
			<Competency name="XSL">
				<TaxonomyId id="Languages"
							description="Languages" />
			</Competency>
			<Competency name="XSLT">
				<TaxonomyId id="Languages"
							description="Languages" />
			</Competency>

			<!-- Concepts/Technologies -->

			<Competency name=".NET Framework">
				<TaxonomyId id="Concepts/Technologies"
							description="Concepts/Technologies" />
			</Competency>
			<Competency name="ADO">
				<TaxonomyId id="Concepts/Technologies"
							description="Concepts/Technologies" />
			</Competency>
			<Competency name="ADO.NET">
				<TaxonomyId id="Concepts/Technologies"
							description="Concepts/Technologies" />
			</Competency>
			<Competency name="ASP">
				<TaxonomyId id="Concepts/Technologies"
							description="Concepts/Technologies" />
			</Competency>
			<Competency name="ASP.NET">
				<TaxonomyId id="Concepts/Technologies"
							description="Concepts/Technologies" />
			</Competency>
			<Competency name="COM/COM+">
				<TaxonomyId id="Concepts/Technologies"
							description="Concepts/Technologies" />
			</Competency>
			<Competency name="Design Patterns">
				<TaxonomyId id="Concepts/Technologies"
							description="Concepts/Technologies" />
			</Competency>
			<Competency name="DTS">
				<TaxonomyId id="Concepts/Technologies"
							description="Concepts/Technologies" />
			</Competency>
			<Competency name="NAnt">
				<TaxonomyId id="Concepts/Technologies"
							description="Concepts/Technologies" />
			</Competency>
			<Competency name="NUnit">
				<TaxonomyId id="Concepts/Technologies"
							description="Concepts/Technologies" />
			</Competency>
			<Competency name="OOP">
				<TaxonomyId id="Concepts/Technologies"
							description="Concepts/Technologies" />
			</Competency>
			<Competency name="SOAP">
				<TaxonomyId id="Concepts/Technologies"
							description="Concepts/Technologies" />
			</Competency>
			<Competency name="Web Services">
				<TaxonomyId id="Concepts/Technologies"
							description="Concepts/Technologies" />
			</Competency>
			<Competency name="WinForms">
				<TaxonomyId id="Concepts/Technologies"
							description="Concepts/Technologies" />
			</Competency>

			<!-- Databases -->

			<Competency name="MS Access">
				<TaxonomyId id="Databases"
							description="Databases" />
			</Competency>
			<Competency name="Oracle">
				<TaxonomyId id="Databases"
							description="Databases" />
			</Competency>
			<Competency name="SQL Server">
				<TaxonomyId id="Databases"
							description="Databases" />
			</Competency>
		</Qualifications>
		<ProfessionalAssociations>
			<Association>
				Name: Laura Bira
				Title: Manager, National Retail Sales
				Company: Anheuser-Busch
				Phone Number: +1 314 577 4740
				Email Address: laura.bira@anheuser-busch.com
			</Association>
			<Association>
				Name: Andrew Hoog
				Title: Director, Information Systems
				Company: TricorBraun
				Phone Number: +1 314 569 3633
				Email Address: ahoog@tricorbraun.com
			</Association>
		</ProfessionalAssociations>
		<Comments>Interests/Hobbies: Spending time with friends and family, programming for learning purposes, meeting new people, discussing relevant social issues and any form of competition</Comments>
		<RevisionDate>2006-06-10</RevisionDate>
	</StructuredXMLResume>
</Resume>